[{"answer": "I'm walking", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Sleeping's better", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah, well, my friend, fact is I've got more than ninety days leave coming", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I thought I'd take some now", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Give me a break, Pops", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " And a lonely ass", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Go ahead", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Whos dead", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah. I follow you", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "lost enough agents for one night", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "That's right. my friend, it seems, has two unique gifts", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Correct the actual list is safe at that place.", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How about if we just go quietly into the bathroom and I wash your mouth out with soap", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend, you've never seen me very upset", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I need one hundred thousand dollars", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Why not? You gave Job a hundred and twenty five thousand", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Really? And you thought if you simply showed up I might give it to you", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Job. Yes, Job is not given to quoting Scripture in his communications. And there was its tone", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Mm", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Very good", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Done. Bring it to me in that place. I want it by the end of the week", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "How will you make sure I'll have the list in three days? It's been a delight. Now where can I drop you dear boy", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You don't think we're going to make it", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You didn't have to........", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Because if you knew what you were getting into, you never would have done it", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Exactly, that's your job. Tomorrow on the train, you can't let this list get out into the open. What's the range of this thing", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Exactly, that's your job. Tomorrow on the train, you can't let this list get out into the open. What's the range of this thing", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'll get you close", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Once we leave the safehouse, get in there and crash. Ill call you from that place", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And get a doctor", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "But why tell us", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What kind of show", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "that place is Job. my friend delivered. How far is he from Luther", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You are my eyes. Stay with him", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Course he did. Just exactly when he knew is something of a question. Before or after I showed in that place, mind telling me, my friend", "docId": "Mission-Impossible.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "They stamped it, didnt they? Those damn that place", "qsentId": 36}]